<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.tvheadend"
       name="Tvheadend Archive"
       version="1.0.4"
       provider-name="Andrebas">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Smart archive browser for Tvheadend DVR recordings</summary>
        <summary lang="sk_SK">Inteligentný prehliadač archívu nahrávok z Tvheadend</summary>
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Inteligentní prohlížeč archivu nahrávek z Tvheadend</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A DVR archive companion for Tvheadend, designed to complement the official pvr.hts client. While pvr.hts handles Live TV, EPG and timers in Kodi's native PVR section, Tvheadend Archive focuses on what pvr.hts does not: browsing the DVR archive grouped by smart categories and subgenres (Films, Series, Sports, News, Shows, Kids, Music, Arts, Docs, Hobby, Other), searching recordings by title without diacritics, and a "Recently watched" history. Live TV is also available as a bonus.</description>
        <description lang="sk_SK">Doplnkový prehliadač DVR archívu pre Tvheadend, navrhnutý ako spoločník k oficiálnemu klientovi pvr.hts. Zatiaľ čo pvr.hts rieši Živé vysielanie, EPG a časovače v natívnej PVR sekcii Kodi, Tvheadend Archive sa zameriava na to, čo pvr.hts nerobí: prechádzanie DVR archívu roztriedeného do inteligentných kategórií a podžánrov (Filmy, Seriály, Šport, Spravodajstvo, Šou, Detské, Hudba, Umenie, Dokumenty, Hobby, Nezaradené), vyhľadávanie nahrávok podľa názvu bez diakritiky a história naposledy pozeraných. Živé vysielanie je tu tiež k dispozícii ako bonus.</description>
        <description lang="cs_CZ">Doplňkový prohlížeč DVR archivu pro Tvheadend, navržený jako společník k oficiálnímu klientovi pvr.hts. Zatímco pvr.hts řeší Živé vysílání, EPG a časovače v nativní PVR sekci Kodi, Tvheadend Archive se zaměřuje na to, co pvr.hts nedělá: procházení DVR archivu roztříděného do inteligentních kategorií a podžánrů (Filmy, Seriály, Sport, Zpravodajství, Show, Dětské, Hudba, Umění, Dokumenty, Hobby, Nezařazené), vyhledávání nahrávek podle názvu bez diakritiky a historie naposledy sledovaných. Živé vysílání je zde také k dispozici jako bonus.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://jurajchudy.sk/</source>
        <news>1.0.4 - Classifier accuracy and diagnostics.

 - Improved: top-level category determination now trusts the DVB-SI Level 1 content_type from the broadcaster over the channel name hint. Channel name was previously overpowering: cooking shows like "MasterChef Junior" on a children's channel went to "Children" even though DVB tagged them as Lifestyle/Hobby; classical concerts on the same channel went to "Children" instead of "Music"; sport channel news items went to "Sports" instead of "News". The new logic uses channel hints only for ambiguous content (content_type 0 = undefined, or 1 = general Movie/Drama, or 5 = Children) where a children's animated series channel really should override DVB. Validated on a 11,650-entry real-world TVH archive across two production servers: 18% of entries shift category, all toward better matches.
 - Added: Documentary channel hints. Broadcasters routinely mistag content on dedicated documentary channels — Discovery, Viasat (Explore/History/Nature/True Crime), National Geographic, Spektrum, Animal Planet, History Channel, BBC Earth, Love Nature, DocuBox, Crime + Investigation — as either Movie/Drama or News. On a 373-entry sample from two such channels, 50% had ct=2 (News) and 48% had ct=1 (Movie/Drama). The new doc channel hints override these mislabels and route the content to Documentaries where it belongs.
 - Added: DVB-SI Level 2 sub-genre nibble decoding. When a recording carries the full 8-bit DVB genre code (about 6.5% of entries) we now use the Level 2 nibble for the sub-category directly — e.g. 0x62 = Classical music, 0xA5 = Cooking, 0x43 = Football, 0x91 = Nature/Animals — instead of falling back to keyword scans. Adds explicit DVB mappings for Sports, News, Shows, Music, Arts, Documentary and Hobby sub-categories.
 - Reduced: false-positive Horror classifications. The Horror keyword pattern previously matched description text like "hrůza války" (horror of war) and mislabelled war films as Horror; on one production archive this misfired on 18 entries. Now requires the horror keyword to appear in the title only (not subtitle or description), and other specific genres like Historical/War, Detective/Crime, Sci-fi, Animation come first in the keyword priority order. Bonus: the Detské keyword fallback no longer matches the generic word "detský" in a plot description, which had been misclassifying home renovation shows as Children's content.
 - Added: optional "Classifier diagnostics" setting (off by default). When enabled, every recording classification is logged with full reasoning — content_type, DVB genre code, channel hint, which rule fired — letting users (and forum reviewers) pinpoint and report specific misclassifications without guesswork.

1.0.3 - Bugfix release responding to first user feedback.

 - Fixed: "Archive by channel" view crashed with "invalid literal for int() with base 10" when TVH HTTP API returned channel numbers as strings or with non-standard formatting. Now uses safe int parsing that handles None, strings, floats, and unicode garbage.
 - Fixed: "Live TV" view crashed with "'>' not supported between instances of 'str' and 'int'" for channel groups containing channels with string-typed numbers.
 - Fixed: HTTP Auth "Auto" mode now defaults to Basic auth (the default in TVH 4.x) with automatic fallback to Digest on 401. Previously it forced Digest regardless, breaking auth for most users.
 - Added: breadcrumb path in the navigation header (e.g. "Archive / Markíza / 2026-05-10" instead of just "Tvheadend Archive") so you can see where you are at every nav depth.
 - Added: full Python traceback in error logs when a handler crashes, for easier future debugging.

1.0.2 - Series grouping fix.

 - Fixed: episodes with combined audio/subtitle flags like "(AD,ST)" or "(HD,DD5.1)" are now correctly grouped under a single series folder. Previously each episode appeared as its own folder because the classifier didn't strip multi-marker parens. Example before: 8 separate "Simpsonovi XXI (N) (AD,ST)" folders; after: one "Simpsonovi XXI" folder with 8 episodes inside.
 - Extended supported tech markers: ST, HD, AD, SS, 3D, UHD, DD, DTS, DD5.1, DTS-HD, DTS-MA, 5.1, 7.1, TT, P.
 - Supported separators inside marker parens: comma or slash, with or without whitespace.

1.0.1 - Resume playback.

 - Recordings now remember where you left off. After stopping playback, Kodi will offer "Resume from X:XX / Start from beginning" the next time you open the same recording.
 - Progress bar overlay on thumbnails in archive listings (visible in skins that support ResumeTime/TotalTime properties, e.g. Estuary).
 - Smart filtering: positions under 30 seconds are not saved (didn't really watch), positions within the last 60 seconds or 95% of length are cleared (watched to end).
 - Cap 500 saved positions, oldest evicted automatically.
 - New settings: "Remember playback position" toggle (default on) and "Clear saved playback positions" action button.

1.0.0 - First public release.

Features:
 - DVR archive browser grouped by smart categories and subgenres (Films, Series, Sports, News, Shows, Kids, Music, Arts, Docs, Hobby, Other). Series are auto-grouped by canonical title across episodes.
 - Alternative archive view "By channel" → date → recording.
 - Live TV with channel tags and "now playing" EPG.
 - Search by recording title — diacritics-insensitive, word-prefix matching (e.g. "kom" finds "Komisař Rex"; "Kriminálka" does NOT match "na"). Two-phase navigation keeps results on screen after playback.
 - Recently watched history — persistent across Kodi restarts, configurable cap, hidden when empty.
 - "Test connection" diagnostic inside Settings.
 - Full Slovak, Czech and English localization.
 - Requires Kodi 19+ (Matrix) and a reachable Tvheadend HTTP server (port 9981 by default). Pairs well with pvr.hts for native PVR features.
</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="repository.andrebas.kodi"
       name="Andrebas Kodi Repository"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="Andrebas">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Andrebas Kodi Repository">
        <dir minversion="19.0.0">
            <info compressed="false">https://mikrotikexe.github.io/kodi-repo/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://mikrotikexe.github.io/kodi-repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://mikrotikexe.github.io/kodi-repo/</datadir>
            <hashes>true</hashes>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Andrebas Kodi addons (Tvheadend Archive and more)</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Repository hosting Kodi addons maintained by Andrebas. Currently includes Tvheadend Archive — a DVR archive browser companion to pvr.hts.</description>
        <summary lang="sk_SK">Kodi doplnky od Andrebasa (Tvheadend Archive a ďalšie)</summary>
        <description lang="sk_SK">Repozitár Kodi doplnkov spravovaných Andrebasom. Zatiaľ obsahuje Tvheadend Archive — prehliadač DVR archívu, ktorý dopĺňa pvr.hts.</description>
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Kodi doplňky od Andrebasa (Tvheadend Archive a další)</summary>
        <description lang="cs_CZ">Repozitář Kodi doplňků spravovaných Andrebasem. Zatím obsahuje Tvheadend Archive — prohlížeč DVR archivu, který doplňuje pvr.hts.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <source>https://github.com/MikrotikExe/kodi-repo</source>
        <news>1.0.0 - Initial release. Hosts plugin.video.tvheadend.</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
